Guide to the Northwest Yearly Meeting Committee and Board records 1918-1989
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives
Northwest Yearly Meeting Committee and Board records
1918-1989
1969-1989
George Fox University and Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Archives 416 North Meridian Street Newberg, Oregon 97132 archives@georgefox.edu http://www.georgefox.edu/offices/murdock/Archives/index.html
Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Church
NWYM.01.13
0.5 cubic feet held in archives box 1/2 sized
Records from the Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends including friends fund, commission on media, board minutes, and executive council minutes.
Item Legacy.348
Collection is available for research.
Willcuts, Jack
Northwest Yearly Meeting of Friends Church; Quakers; Society of Friends
Religion
- Friends Fund, 1973-1979; 1/1; 1 folders
- Evangelical Friends Mission, 1981; 1/2; 1 folders
- Board of Education, 1979-1980; 1/3; 1 folders
- Yearly Meeting Long Range Planning, 1982; 1/4; 1 folders
- Commission on Media- Media Board Minutes, 1969-1989; 1/5; 1 folders
- Commission on Media, 1981-1985; 1/6; 1 folders
- Commission on Media- Media Board Minutes, 1976-1979; 1/7; 1 folders
- Commission on Media- Media Board Minutes, 1971-1975; 1/8; 1 folders
- Commission on Media- Media Board Minutes, 1968-1970; 1/9; 1 folders
- Commission on Ministry, 1960-1980; 1/10; 1 folders
- Social Concerns, 1979-1980; 1/11; 1 folders
- Spiritual Life Ministry and Counsel, 1979-1980; 1/12; 1 folders
- Stewardship, 1979-1980; 1/13; 1 folders
- Stewardship Publicity, 1963-1969; 1/14; 1 folders
- Minutes - Board of Stewardship, 1955-1974; 1/15; 1 folders
- Executive Council NWYM Correspondence and Minutes, 1979-1980; 1/16; 1 folders
- Friends Church Extension Foundation, 1975; 1/17; 1 folders
- Friends Church Extension Foundation Part 2, 1962-1980; 1/18; 1 folders